Jurriaan Engels

Jurriaanengels@hotmail.nl

Amsterdam, Berlin

Website

<u>LinkedIn</u>

Analytically minded data scientist/data analyst with a passion for data visualization, data knowledge, and statistics. I am excited to share my insights and experience wih a team of likeminded individuals where questions lead to new discoveries and high-quality data analytics.

WORK EXPERIENCE

A.S.R. - Junior Consultant (Data Science Traineeship via House of Bèta) December 2022 – Januari 2023

- Build sustainable relationships and trust with customer accounts through open and interactive communication while following communication procedures, guidelines and policies.
- Providing both specific content-related and general information about products, policies and services
 of life insurances at A.S.R.

TNO - Graduate Intern September 2021 – May 2022

- Researched privacy enhancing techniques and how to combine these with graph neural networks in order to generate privacy preserving graphical transaction data.
- Providing entry-level knowledge of this subject to the data science department through presentations and setting them up for a bigger related project.
- Worked with several data scientists at TNO and two data scientists from two different financial institutions in order to define the quality metrics of the model.

EDUCATION

University of Amsterdam - Master's, Mathematics (Specialization: Stochastics and Statistics) September 2019 – May 2022 **University of Amsterdam** - Bachelor's, Mathematics September 2016 – July 2019

SKILLS

Python, R, Apache Spark, Azure Databricks, Git, Excel, VBA, SQL, PowerBI, Tableau, LaTeX, HTML, CSS.

COURSES/TRAININGS

Statistical Data Analysis (UvA), Advanced Machine Learning (MasterMath), Dynamic Programming and Reinforcement Learning (MasterMath), Kickstart Excel, VBA, Python (HoB). Full list on request.

CERTIFICATES

<u>Agile Scrum Foundation</u> (Finished)— Basic fundamentals of agile and scrum projectplanning techniques and how to apply them in practice.

<u>Machine Learning: A to Z</u> (Finished) - Course on data preprocessing, regression, classification, clustering, RL, NLP, deep learning, dimensionality reduction and model selection in Python and R.

<u>IBM Data Science</u> **(9.4 over 10 courses)** - Course on importing and cleaning datasets, analyze and visualize data, and build and evaluate machine learning models in Python and R.

<u>IBM Applied AI</u> (Ongoing) - Creating AI chatbots, website deployment, AI-powered solutions with APIs, OpenCV, Image classification, cloud deployment, deep learning models.

<u>IBM Advanced Data Science</u> (Ongoing) - Fully scalable end to end data integration, deep learning pipelines, Apache Spark, SparkML, TensorFlow, Keras, Pytorch, Deeplearning4J, Apache CouchDB, MQTT.